<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://prpkprpk.github.io</id>
    <title>PRPK.com | Predictions | Reveries | Possibilities | Kaleidoscope</title>
    <updated>2025-01-20T06:07:12.100Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://prpkprpk.github.io"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://prpkprpk.github.io/atom.xml"/>
    <subtitle>Perdictions, Reveries, Possibilities and Kaleidoscope? Just a joke. prpk.com is only a storyless domain name registered by my father 20 years ago, rolling his keyboard, when the storage of 4-letter domain names was in an emergency. It could be something like nwsc.com or eodk.com.

Of course, none of these sites is available, because they came from me rolling my keyboard either.

There are great sites like xkcd.com, and believe it or not, I discovered it through rolling my keyboard when I was only 12!</subtitle>
    <logo>https://prpkprpk.github.io/images/avatar.png</logo>
    <icon>https://prpkprpk.github.io/favicon.ico</icon>
    <rights>All rights reserved 2025, PRPK.com | Predictions | Reveries | Possibilities | Kaleidoscope</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WORLDBUILDING]]></title>
        <id>https://prpkprpk.github.io/post/worldbuilding/</id>
        <link href="https://prpkprpk.github.io/post/worldbuilding/">
        </link>
        <updated>2024-10-29T02:49:34.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>WORLDBUILDING</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[what if]]></title>
        <id>https://prpkprpk.github.io/post/what-if/</id>
        <link href="https://prpkprpk.github.io/post/what-if/">
        </link>
        <updated>2024-10-29T02:48:39.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>what if</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Retribution]]></title>
        <id>https://prpkprpk.github.io/post/retribution/</id>
        <link href="https://prpkprpk.github.io/post/retribution/">
        </link>
        <updated>2024-09-02T03:58:39.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Listen! Do you believe that there are gods in the world? If you are a materialist or an atheist, the question is just silly to you. But, remember, there is a god, the god of nature, whom you should never deny. You know, I’ve hunted in the forest in the northwest of Russia, and as a professional hunter, I have seen the god of nature raging in the desolated forest. This is the most absurd, most ridiculous story you may have ever heard, but I’m still going to tell you the whole story, the story about the god of nature. You may think that I’m crazy. I might be crazy, but listen, please, never show your irrespective to the god of nature.</p>
<p>It was the 17th year that I spent in the forest in the Northwest Forest in Russia. I was tired of hunting in the forest, and always made malicious swears that I would stop hunting after selling the last horn I had got from the elks. However, as you know, selling horns was just too profitable so I kept on selling dozens of horns and breaking my swears one by another. One day, after swearing again, I finally shot my gun. I could hear the birds fleeting from their nest, making squeezed sounds, and elks, ran away in all directions, leaving disordered footprints on the undefiled ground, disrupting the harmony of snow in a barbaric way. The disorder only lasted for a few seconds, as a giant body fell to the ground, dying the snow with crimson blood, signaling the death of a beautiful creature. It was a cold winter afternoon, and my legs and arms were freezing cold. I put down my scruffy shotgun and walked incongruously towards the poor animal.</p>
<p>You know, as a professional hunter, I was especially strong and was good at dealing with all kinds of animals, and also, without any sympathy. You know, sympathy is just useless for hunters. I saw the air with a saw, cutting off the giant horn of the elk. The animal’s body trembled unconsciously, tossing out dark red blood and pale cerebrum into the sky; bones and muscles were broken by the sharp tool, making an enjoyable chunking sound. The crimson and the blood were just so satisfying that I wanted to continue hunting forever, till I died. I just completely forgot my swear and carried the body of the elk towards my wooden cabin.</p>
<p>I wonder if I had gone a little far that day, and I spent the whole afternoon hurrying to my cabin with the bloody flesh of the animal, leaving a bloody line right after my footprint, creating a beautiful scene in the world of purity and snow. The sun had already gone down, beyond the horizon as I opened the door of my small cabin. So far, everything has been normal and smooth throughout the day. Remember I’ve talked about the god of nature? I wonder if I was frustrated by my untrustworthy swear and he just let out his anger on my small cabin without even warning me. Just as I opened the door, something fell to the ground, heavily, with a deafening sound, hitting the wooden ground, like a bell on the church, judging the renegade with its unlimited power. The sound reverberated in my ears, as the object flew right over my nose, and I could feel the object cutting my hair rudely with the sharp angle. I could feel my heart stop beating for a second, as the heavy object rolled, breaking into pieces.</p>
<p>You know, although I was frightened by the weird object, I could still act bravely toward a thrilling occasion. I kicked onto the object inadvertently, and as I looked down, a skeleton was staring at me in the roaring sound of broken bones, with its empty eye sockets and raised nose and mouse. I was shocked at once, but, you know, as I was familiar with all kinds of skeletons, and I suddenly noticed that it was the skull of an elk.</p>
<p>All at once, anger just ran through my fragile nerves and brain. I did the most regretful thing I’d ever done through my whole life: I kicked on the skeleton heavily, with my heavy boots and sturdy muscle, striking the whole skull with unbelievable force. The skull moaned, rotating, and finally, when I looked down, I could feel the cold, callous sight striking on my face, with fire in the eyes, giving out the anger of being killed and insulted. The sight went through my body, freezing my blood, reminding me about the silly swear I’d made dozens of times. However, the feeling just escaped from my naïve spirit within a few seconds, you know, as I was not religious, and at that time, I thought I would never be religious. I just threw the skeleton and swept the fragments into the deep snow outside my cabin.</p>
<p>Just as I said, there were certainly gods in the world, but at that time, I was just like a naughty child and was not aware of what I was doing. I remembered that I had put the skull of an elf on the ceiling of the cabin as a decoration, and I just ignored the confusing fall off of the skeleton. I went into my cozy small hut, set up the fire, and went to my quilt with tiredness.</p>
<p>I was woken up by the sound of the wind at midnight. You know, you couldn’t have a good dream on a windy night, especially in the deep dark forest. You have to be vigilant all the time, driving away the curious animals and paying attention to the bad weather. The fire had already gone out, and the room was totally dark, even without moonlight. The ashes were shining in the fireplace, generating eerie light, just as the eyes of a starving bear, searching for victims for dinner. I looked outside the small window: it was snowing heavily, and tons of snowflakes were floating in the freezing air.</p>
<p>“What a dam bad weather.” I thought as I got up that I couldn’t sleep for even another single second. Bam! The environment was lighted up by a pale light, tearing a hole in the sky, and shining the trees and stones around the building. I jumped up, and in the meantime, I noticed how silly I was: it was only extreme weather, common in the forest. I just lay down again and tried to sleep.</p>
<p>The darkness continued, and just after I lay in bed, I began to notice something strange happening: I heard a strange cracking sound, wondering outside the dark night. I knew you would never believe in me, but listen! This was exactly what had frightened me. You know, I lived in the forest for over ten years, and I had never heard about something that was active in the darkness of night. The elks were resting, and the bears hibernated, and you know, no one lived in the dark forest besides hunters like me. I tried to ignore the strange sound, relieving myself that it was only the sound of snow, but as the cracking sound grew louder and circled my small hut, I could not bear it anymore.</p>
<p>I got up from my bed for the second time, looking out from the small window carefully: nothing had changed: looming snowflakes continued to scrabble across the window from time to time, and the stumps and the fences looming in the argenteus screen. Everything stood in stagnation, without moving a little bit, even without a single footstep. Everything was in peace, except the strange sound kept disturbing my fragile eardrum.</p>
<p>The night was totally a mystery. It was strange, and thrilling, trying to punish me in some confusing ways, but I was embarrassed by my foolishness and arrogance on that cold winter night. I felt ashamed of my stupid decision, that I just went to bed without thinking, as the confusing sound hovered, going round and round, even on the ceiling of my cabin.</p>
<p>The sound finally disappeared in front of the door, and as I was celebrating the silly annoying sound disappearing the door began to shake irregularly within a few seconds. At first, only dust and ashes were on the shelves and the door fell down, but combined with a shuffling sound, the room soon trembled on a much bigger scale. Just like a small hut in a hurricane, all kinds of objects including books, animal bones, and bullets fell from different places, making the room a mess. I was terrified, jumping up from my bed, shouting “Who’s there?” Just as you expected, no one replied, as the disaster continued, trying to destroy my cabin in the most impolite way. Ashes began to get out of the fireplace, igniting the wooden floor, and keeping the temperature in the small hut rising.</p>
<p>You know, no one can keep calm in a terrifying situation, and so do I. Although as a hunter, with superhuman courage and strength, it took me some time to recover from the terrifying scene. I tried to convince myself that it was only an earthquake, no, a tornado, that Russia never had earthquakes, but I still grabbed my gun and kicked the door open. “who’s there?” I shouted in a trembling voice, but the only thing that replied to me was the raging snowstorm. Nothing was there. I shot into the dark night, but the bullets were absorbed by the snow and the wind.</p>
<p>The crackling sound of the woodfire dragged my soul back, reminding me of being burnt to death. I hurried into the dark forest with freezing arms and trembling legs. The hut was getting away from me, and after everything went in silence, I looked back to the hut looming in the snowstorm. I saw the most terrifying scene you may think I was mad. There was a huge elk on the top of the roof, carrying a huge stick with fire on the top, and hundreds of elks circled around the small cabin, with fire and smoke rising from dust and ashes. The fire burning, depriving my soul, weakening my leg, striking my fragile nerves. I ran as fast as I could, trying to avoid the misfortune falling on my fate.</p>
<p>I left the forest as fast as could.</p>
<p>You know, I disrespected nature, disrespected god, and finally, I was disrespected by them too. I never went back to the forest again, but if you would like to revisit nature, please, remember that there were gods in the world, and please remember to show respect to them.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Rebellion?]]></title>
        <id>https://prpkprpk.github.io/post/the-rebellion/</id>
        <link href="https://prpkprpk.github.io/post/the-rebellion/">
        </link>
        <updated>2024-08-15T04:23:37.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>John was sitting in the small command room, facing a holographic table, wondering about the civil war. Blue and red light shaded his face, submerging his emotions and feelings behind the cold barrier, depriving happiness, sympathy, felicity, despair, fear, and hesitation, from his body, his soul.</p>
<p>Everything was in silence, in the darkness, except the faint sound of gunfire passing from the distance. Under the dim moonlight, a huge board was hanging on the wall, with the words “Freedom, Equality, Justice.” A small water tank, the home of a fish, stood in the corner. John squatted down, facing the small water tank, watching the small golden fish diving deep in the water, like a taxus leaf trembling in the cold autumn. The fish had laid in a shallow puddle, waiting for death to fall behind, and John took it back for no reason, even though water was a scarce resource three years ago.</p>
<p>Knock, knock. John’s mind was pulled back. A man went inside, with a handgun on his belt and two small boxes in his hands. John was not surprised by his arrival. He stood up and faced the man with his glasses.</p>
<p>“What’s going on, Mathew?”</p>
<p>The man put one of the boxes on the table: “I’ve just confirmed the information from our scientists, and we’ve got these small demons.” He pointed to the box on the table in an unusual tone: “θ rays’ generator.”</p>
<p>“7 kinds of different radioactive elements were separated in small columns inside, and all the columns were surrounded by lead and they won’t react.”</p>
<p>Mathew paused for a moment, took a deep breath, and began to speak in a slow, serious voice, mixing with a sense of extreme fear. He picked up the box, holding two of the corners: “The balance will be disrupted if you push the two corners heavily.” He paused again, “All the elements will be mixed up and a proton will be injected into the mixture. Quarks will be rephotographed into an upper state called a θ particle. It will lead to unstoppable fusion in nearby atoms, generating more θ particles, and finally lead to the collapse of all the atoms on earth.”</p>
<p>John made no reply as if he was listening to a fairytale.</p>
<p>“Bam!” Something exploded with a thunder-like voice. The board fell down to the earth, and the tank, trembling, making friction sounds, finally fell onto the ground. Water flew across the wooden floor, rushing through the books, the dust, electric wires, and finally, the huge board. Words were filtered by the water, blooming like dying flowers, blurring. The room was ruined. The holograph flickering, and then the words, the world sinking into the darkness.</p>
<p>The sound of gunfire went closer, mixed with the shouting and crying of soldiers. John came back to himself, watching the humid ground, searching for something “Let it go. It will be fine.” He murmured</p>
<p>Dim light shading through transparent windows, signaling the approaching of daybreak. John opened the shabby door, and walked out of the small command room without even turning around: “Send all the information to the government and tell them to stop fire on our army in thirty minutes.”</p>
<p>Mathew stood up, “It is not our goal! It is also not the goal of the Defiance! Do you know that this is likely to ruin our civilization?”</p>
<p>“It is a command, Mathew.” John disappeared with his voice in the dark corridor. “We get no choice. That’s the only way to change the world, the wars, and the inequalities.”</p>
<p>Three hours later</p>
<p>John walked out from the shelter of the Defiance for the first time. It was a cold morning, dew covering the lawn with water, wetting the shoes and the trousers, rushing the glory and the honor of the Defiance. He started the Defiance three years ago, beating hundreds of thousands of enemies. He had witnessed the slaves, the workers, the poor, the oppressions. Once, a total stranger, a brave fighter saved him from being blown up with his life. He could never forget the mangled body and the hopeful sight, praying to him “Live on, keep determined.” He could remember the joy of receiving new weapons and comrades, the excitement of fighting on the battlefield, and the sorrows of the death of friends and soldiers.</p>
<p>Everything had gone, he thought. The world remained unchanged. The wine and meat stink, but the road was frozen to death. The laughter and the freedom in the liberated area were gone, and dreams collapsed.</p>
<p>John held the box tight. He stood in the shadow, back on the ruin, back on the rising sun. The sun finally rose above the ground, shining golden light on the surface of the earth, illuminating their enemy’s body on the opposite side of the lawn, dying the grass, the tree, the soil with all kinds of pigments, and covering them in the completely dark shadow of the ruin.</p>
<p>He took out the small box, holding the two corners, hanging it overhead, into the brightness of the sun. The box reflected the sunlight, shining, with metallic luster. “How beautiful.”</p>
<p>He felt a blow to his stomach. He could felt the hot liquid leaked out. It was blood. He turned around, with astonishment, finding out Mathew stood with his arm lifted, carrying his handgun from his belt. His arm was shaking, but his voice was not trembling anymore: “No matter what he becomes, whether he is full of sin and blood, or with equality, harmony, and hope, he should not be erased for no reason. No one is qualified to pass judgment on him.” John’s vision blurred as Mathew passed through his body, walking towards the sunlight, towards the enemy.</p>
<p>“Sorry about that,” Mathew spoke in a low voice as John’s body collapsed, and he shouted at the top of his voice, “the Defiance, surrendered.”</p>
<p>Mathew continued walking forward, passing a small stream, with a golden fish swimming happily and freely, towards the future, towards the far river.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The MagIcal Pen]]></title>
        <id>https://prpkprpk.github.io/post/the-magical-pen/</id>
        <link href="https://prpkprpk.github.io/post/the-magical-pen/">
        </link>
        <updated>2024-07-02T04:27:19.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>A pen, a miracle, was created by the god, and discarded in the world through a careless wave. Everyone who picked the pen would receive three chances to draw something and wish it to be true.</p>
<p>The pen fell to the ground, in the shape of an ordinary sign pen, lying in an ordinary shop with dozens of students. The one who came across the pen was a naive boy. He luckily picked the pen out from thousands of similar objects and drew a line on a flat piece of paper. Astonishingly, the line jumped out from the page, floated in the air, and began to swim like a black snake. The boy was shocked, with his mouse in an O shape and saliva on his jaw. He secretly picked up the pen and hurried home without even paying the price.</p>
<p>At night, while the moon was hanging in the sky high, the boy picked up his pen, opened his homework, and charming: “grand, magical, wishing pen, making my homework being done.” The pen lay on the blank workbook, making nothing except a humming sound, seemingly refusing the stupid wish. The boy took another workbook from piles of different books, charming with his soft, pride sound, but following with nothing again.</p>
<p>The boy sat in front of his desk with disappointment. He hesitated for a moment, and finally took out a piece of paper, drawing with his shaking, furious hand. He draws a gray box, a bottle of ink, and piles of finished workbooks in front of the gray box. The box then jumped out of the page and appeared in the boy’s hand. The boy picked up a page and stuffed it inside the box. Lines of different words and sentences appeared on the page, following the with a horrible, cracking sound. The boy, astonished by the miracle of the small, powerful pen, plugged all of his unfinished homework into the small box and waited anxiously until all the homework was done.</p>
<p>The next day, the boy went to school with tons of books and papers, handing them to the teacher with a proud smile. Ignoring his classmates’ unbelieving discussion and the teacher’s wide-opening eyes, he put all his homework on the platform. With a satisfied smile, the teacher opened the first assignment, but then a roar of extreme anger pulled the boy back from his reverie. Unbelievably, the boy opened the workbook and found out that all the words were unrecognizable.</p>
<p>The boy went back home with a depressed heart. He took out the pen and drew a huge cross on the box. The cross jumped out, as the pen jumped into the air, turned into ashes, and faded in the falling sun. The boy smashed the box on the ground, crying as the pen left him forever.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Catching an Asteroid]]></title>
        <id>https://prpkprpk.github.io/post/catching-an-asteroid/</id>
        <link href="https://prpkprpk.github.io/post/catching-an-asteroid/">
        </link>
        <updated>2024-06-24T04:31:55.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>“The asteroid is going to hit the earth after only a few hours. Scientists are still unsure about where will the asteroid fall. For safety reasons, we strongly recommend residents to stay home and close the windows, so that the shock wave will not hurt your eardrums. Now, Let’s turn the channel to professor Paign, a professor who has been ……”</p>
<p>I turned down the channel. People’s speaking now became mussy shuffling sounds, humming around my ears. Driving home, focusing on the passing pedestrians and monotonous streetscape, I let out a breath.</p>
<p>“What about the rents? Could you manage to pay the bill two days earlier?” Asked Jack, who was sitting as a copilot, playing his phone, focusing on a silly card game, popularizing the whole country in only a few days.”</p>
<p>“Maybe. But it is obvious that it’s easier for you to get those extra money. Superexcellent employee, uh?” I answered back, “Are you sure it is sensible for a freshman to ask for salary?”</p>
<p>“Hey, no time for quarreling.” Jacked murmured, “The thing is, we have to pay the bill two days later, and our employer will not pay us a single cent.” He stopped, “and the rent, will cost us an arm and a leg.”</p>
<p>I kept silent. Everyone knew that it was an economic downturn. People were losing their jobs, and it was likely that we would be the next one. It was still light outside, but cloud was filling the sky. Everything was losing its color.</p>
<p>“……so, it is assumed that the asteroid is made of metal, probably precious mental. Therefore, it is hard for the asteroid to vaporize in the earth’s atmosphere. Plus, I strongly recommend that people who live downtown evacuate, because according to the latest calculations, there is more than an 80% chance that this meteorite will land in the park ……”</p>
<p>“Wait, you mean, precious metal?” Jack jumped up from the chair, but immediately caught by the seatbelt, hurting his nose. “So, is it possible, I mean, to get a piece of asteroid, so that we could sell it at a high price?”</p>
<p>“Don’t be silly.” On the other side of the road, a car speeded behind us, heading downtown. I pay full attention to avoid crashing into the crazy driver. “No one will be able to catch the asteroid. We will pay it with our life.”</p>
<p>“It is not the case.” Jack answered with confidence, “It is possible, I mean, possible, for us to get a piece of debris of the asteroid. The debris is probably made in silver, or even gold, and we could pay for our rent.”</p>
<p>“Oh, would you pay the rent with your life?”</p>
<p>“Do you know what will happen if we cannot pay for the rent?” Jack asked.</p>
<p>Silently, I agreed with him. He was right. We would be killed by the freezing weather. We would be kicked out of our cozy bed, lying on the street, feeling temperature going away from our chilling body. We had no other choice. We had to catch the asteroid—or at least, some pieces—with our hands.</p>
<p>Without hesitation, I turned the car around and turned the radio back on. Without knowing the exact time when the asteroid would hit the ground, I put my foot on the gas heavily. The car trembled, and rushing towards downtown.</p>
<p>We all assumed that everyone who lived downtown would be scrambling to get out. However, I was wrong. Our journey back was not very smooth. I would not describe the highway as “crowded”, but still, some cars were rushing back with us, and some, were even faster.</p>
<p>“Crazy!” Jack exclaimed, “Are they going to catch the asteroid, just like us?”</p>
<p>“No idea.” I replied. A huge truck rushing over us, whistling loudly. “The truck must be overspeed.”</p>
<p>The night falls, and not a while, we arrived at the park downtown. The downtown area had lost its usual buzz. Street vendors had already taken refuge, and there was no light in the Windows of residential buildings. “……The asteroid is going to hit the ground within thirty minutes. Again, we advise residents in the lower city to evacuate as soon as possible to prevent unnecessary loss of life and property……”</p>
<p>I looked up. The meteorite is clearly visible from the ground. Bright yellow flashes make the deep blue night sky as bright as day. It got bigger, bigger, bigger……</p>
<p>Ashes were blown up from the street, creating a foggy world. Then, fire alarm started to ring, with orange fire coming out from the fog. I just felt a pair of big hands pushing my head down. “The announcement of the broadcast is inaccurate! The asteroid has landed! Get down and cover your ears!” I couldn’t see anything but the world of dust that filled my vision.</p>
<p>All of sudden, the car window shattered, breaking into shards of glass, streaking across my sight. I felt a sharp pain in my hand—the glass had definitely cut the back of my hand. Then, through the palm of my hand covering my ears, there was a deafening bang. There is no doubt that if I had not covered my ears, I would have lost my hearing.</p>
<p>I looked upwards. A shiny, firing piece was flying towards me. It was a piece of asteroid, I thought. However, it was burning, and obviously I could not catch it with my hands， so I decided to  pick it up when it cooled down. “Hey, Jack, I think we found a meteorite. We’re going to be rich!” As I was shouting, a figure rushed out of the fog and reached out to pick up the splinter.</p>
<p>We didn’t even know there were people fighting over meteorite fragments with us. “Stop! That’s our piece!” Jack was the first to react and rushed out of the car door, shielding the meteorite with his arm. Then his arm began to burn. Jack started screaming. “Please call an ambulance…… ” I shouted. However, it disappeared, leaving a thick smoke and a twisty human body.</p>
<p>Two days later</p>
<p>In the empty room, a TV was performing the news. “…… The man who tried to collect meteorite fragments were seriously hurt. He believed that the meteorite was made of precious metals. His arm was badly burned. However, in fact this meteorite is made of copper…”</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The urequited love]]></title>
        <id>https://prpkprpk.github.io/post/the-urequited-love/</id>
        <link href="https://prpkprpk.github.io/post/the-urequited-love/">
        </link>
        <updated>2024-05-21T04:37:11.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>“Due to inflicting harm on a human, Teddy Bear-2231……” The announcement was devoid of emotion, judging my fate, but I wouldn’t change my decision; I’d always protect my boy from the evils of summer.</p>
<p>I recalled that fateful summer—the moment I became aware in a dank, gloomy basement. I felt unbearable pain as I saw cotton, stained by ash and dirty water, scattered on the freezing concrete floor. I struggled to gather the pieces of my broken body.</p>
<p>Bang! With a loud bang, I suddenly froze, sitting back to the cold floor—a toy’s instinct. Toys were not likely to move, obviously, and I didn’t want to be an exception. Within a few seconds, a boy rushed in and pushed the heavy, wooden door with all his might. He was short, looked no more than 12 years old, with mud on his face trembling with fear. I could feel the violence of the guys who were pushing and smashing the wooden door. The boy stood, looked over his shoulder at me, and all of the sudden, jumped right at me with a cry. “Sorry, sorry, sorry……It’s my fault……I forgot to lock the door today. Please don’t be scared. Winter’s coming, and no one will harm you anymore……”</p>
<p>Winter? Oh, sorry for that. I forgot to tell you that no one live in this place can expose themselves in the chilly winter. They will turn into an ice cube within only a few seconds. So that’s the case: someone, or maybe a group of people, decided to harm the boy, and when winter came, no one would be able to access to this basement, and thus harm the boy.</p>
<p>As I was wondering, the boy dug a needle and thread out of the cabinet, carrying on his hands. “Wait, I’m going to repair you first.” He picked up a pile of cotton that I had put away and then thrown on the floor, as if he picked up a pile of treasure, and finally, stuffed them into my already wizened body. “I’m now going to seam your body. This is going to hurt a little, but please bear with me.” I could feel the needles passing through my skin, and finally, with a flourishing ending, he told me that it was over.</p>
<p>He then asked for my help with a wounded arm, but I couldn’t answer; my toyish limitations silenced me. I can’t respond to him right now, limited by the teddy bear’s body. Disappointed, the boy walked away to his bed, without even making a sound.</p>
<p>Toys were sensitive to time, and as time elapse, I could feel the sun going down the hill, and night fell onto the earth. I could imagine that the boy had been taking care of me for a long time, keeping me out of harm’s way, and expecting me to do something for him. The boy’s snoring was striking my ear drum from the corner. I thought it was time to do something for him. I can’t be silent any longer.</p>
<p>I slipped out through the basement air duct and ran to a store under cover of night. It was night, freezing wind coming across the street. It was already late summer, and winter was approaching. The boy would not be bullied by those people, I thought, as I picked up a tube full of unguent which could release the pain. This might help, I thought, as I came out from the shop and noticed a group of children.</p>
<p>“What about pepper spray?”</p>
<p>“Oh god, stop kidding. He could even forget his way home.”</p>
<p>“We could control him easily. You know what, he only owns a small basement, and within a few days, he would beg us to provide him a place to live in winter!”</p>
<p>“Haha……”</p>
<p>The boys walked past the street lamp beside me, not noticing me in the dark. I could feel the cotton rattling inside me. I was furious. Quietly, I followed them, remembering their accommodation.</p>
<p>That night, a legend was added to the city: there is a teddy bear who loves everything, and will not hesitate to hold everyone he loves until death, never to let go. All the people who suffocated, their mouth will hang a faint smile.</p>
<p>“Eliminating all memories. Counting down: 10, 9, 8, ……” The humming sound of a machine surrounded me, pulling my thought back to the place. I closed my eyes, smiled. If the boy brings me the purest, childlike, unrequited love, then I will also go through fire and water, with the power of, unrequited love.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tossing a coin]]></title>
        <id>https://prpkprpk.github.io/post/tossing-a-coin/</id>
        <link href="https://prpkprpk.github.io/post/tossing-a-coin/">
        </link>
        <updated>2024-05-17T04:41:24.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The sun went down at the peak of the mountain, leaving the world a hazy, orange scene, with a peaceful and harmony beam shooting on the side of the table. I sat on the rusty old chair, leaning the small chair backward, with a squeak, cacophony sound, disturbed the peaceful world. Pens and all kinds of pigments made most of the space inside the room, occupying the only void in the small room, covered with dust, losing its original color.</p>
<p>Inside the small room, there were two beds, my brother’s and mine, with tidy and simple quilts and sheets. The sheets were white and clean at first, but years after years, it was polluted by the soot and gas, with a grey and white appearance. We were all miners, working in a colliery for over five years.</p>
<p>Knock, knock. The door opened and a tall, stout man with dark skin and high cheekbones came in, carrying with him a pickaxe and a huge bag covered with dirty mud. My brother was back. He was strong, mature, with big eyes full of determination. He worn a suspender trousers, sank by soot and sweat, just like most of the miners. I hurried towards him, taking the huge bag, and found dozens of toothpaste-like tubes. The tubes, compared to the rusty old bag, looked especially shiny and elegant, with uncommon words like crimson, azure and ultramarine writing on the back. “Hum, the new painting appears good, and I bought them with a whole gold coin! You can use them to paint and stop collecting those dirty minerals!” (P.S. painter suffered from poverty in the 16thto 17th century make paintings by themselves by picking colorful stones and making them into dye) My brother shouted. Without waiting me to reply, he continued, “And good news. We can begin painting next Monday.”</p>
<p>The words magically stroke on my nerve, just like an electric shock touching my skin. I jumped up, but still with hesitation: “What about the bread and butter? We cannot pay for the rice and barley without working for 18 hours a day in the colliery.”</p>
<p>My brother smiled secretly, bending his head to my ears, and whispered: “I have been saving my salary for a whole month, and now, we can pay for our living in the next week without working anymore!” We smiled towards each other, packing up all the pens, pigments and drawing boards, and began to brush the colors on the papers. Sun went down and the city was covered by darkness, but a small beam of light ejected the small window, leaving an abyss of light and art in the chaotic night, bringing out happiness and beautifulness from the small room.</p>
<p>Days passed and we painted pictures after pictures. The room was completely a mess now: the floor was covered with all kinds of pigments and our cold turkey, the quilts were totally a mess that we never folded them, and even the ceiling was dyed with a few colors. I was sitting at the center, with red circle under my eyes, painting the yellow sunflowers just like the great masterpiece of Vincent Van Gogh. The sun went westward, reminding me that I had to paint quicker or there would be no time for me to finish my masterpiece. My brother went out to sell his work in the market for food and candles, and the room was in silence besides paintbrush shuffling through the paper.</p>
<p>It was the last day of the week, and our deposit was depleted. We had to work or starved to death. During the past seven days, I painted and practiced a lot, with an intolerable question unsolved: I couldn’t paint the lines well. As a “professional” painter studying art for years, I had never met such silly questions like this, and it became even weird when my brother found out he couldn’t make a simple line straight, either.</p>
<p>The door trembled and my brother came expressionless. All of his painting was on his back, and his money bag was nearly empty. It looked like his works were not welcomed.</p>
<p>“Listen.” he called me with his coarse, hoarse throat.</p>
<p>I put down my paintbrush, starring at him, frustrated for being disrupted.</p>
<p>“I think you noticed something uncommon for all of us. We couldn’t paint those basic lines and curves well. We have taken classes in private schools, and are not supposed to make those simple mistakes.”</p>
<p>I nodded my head, suggesting him to continue.</p>
<p>“I have a plan. Now, it’s the time for us to toss a coin,” he said with excitement, “and the one who gets the ‘head’ side will attend the art college; the one who gets “tail” side will work in the mine for four years, until the one who attends the college graduated. Then, we would change our side. After eight years, we will be able to create masterpieces both.”</p>
<p>“Why should we do that?” I asked with a trembling voice.</p>
<p>My brother healed a breath, “We could do much better in drawing if there is a chance for us to study continuously and professionally, and this is the only way for us to improve our painting skills.” Seeing the longing and the hope in my eyes, he said to me with a sense of commitment: “Now, you first.” He put down the money bag, and picked a coin from his pocket.</p>
<p>Taking over the coin from my brother’s hand, and without carefully observing the coin, I threw it into the air without waiting. The coin began to rotate at great speed, floating in the air, reflecting the golden sunlight shooting in the room. My heart skipped a bit, as if someone had pinched it hardly. I starred at the coin with a piercing eye, starring at it as it falling down, down, down to the ground with a sound of mental colliding. It then rolled across the floor, fell down, with the “head” side.</p>
<p>My heart relaxed, and I jumped up just like an exciting kangaroo, rushing to the door, as if I would like to tell it to the whole world. My brother watched me in the shadows, smiling towards me, happily and regretfully.</p>
<p>Four years later:</p>
<p>I stood on the huge stage with all of my classmates, winning a certificate as an artist. Despite the excitement of graduation, I couldn’t wait to tell my brother that he could attend the college he dreamed day and night. I grabbed the certification and hurried towards the station to the colliery, to the place of my brother. I didn’t contact to my brother often due to my schoolwork, but I could feel the passionate in his writing and his words.</p>
<p>I finally met my brother in the darkness underground. He noticed my certification, and tried to speak a few sentences. He made great efforts, but in the end, he only gives me his hands with shivering.</p>
<p>I lowered my head: it was a hand of an ordinary miner, full of wrinkle and scars. For years, it worked under great pressure, submerged by water, burned by fire and sliced by pungent stones and coal. The blue veins humped, just like infected blood flowing in the blood vessels of a dying patient. His hands shaking and trembling, couldn’t even carry my certification.</p>
<p>“My hands cannot hold brushes, and will not be able to hold it either.” He said the words in a low voice. His voice was even more hoarse after not seeing him for several months. The words were like gavels, judging his life and his fate in the most crucial way, snuffing his ways towards art and his dream. We stood still in silence, without speaking a word. The shade of the candles covered my brother’s strong but hunchbacked body, leaving me in the light. He sobbed, leaving tears and snots.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ghost In a Museum]]></title>
        <id>https://prpkprpk.github.io/post/ghost-in-a-museum/</id>
        <link href="https://prpkprpk.github.io/post/ghost-in-a-museum/">
        </link>
        <updated>2024-04-08T08:20:14.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The British Museum was magnificent—as magnificent as I expected—oh, it may be even more sublime, more gorgeous than I expected. It was just the grandest, literally, museum in the world. The furniture was luxurious, with gold insets and velvet intersperse, lying on every single side of each giant room. Tons of ancient relics were lying in the glass showcase, reflecting the soft golden light generated by chandeliers, signaling the profound history of cultures and civilizations. The first week was relaxing and enjoyable, but as I was retreating to the Warfield of Treasure and History on a dim Friday, I noticed something uncommon.</p>
<p>It was a Friday afternoon, with millions of millions of liquids cluttered on the top of the British city, I was wandering across the complicated corridors when suddenly I noticed a dark shadow behind a giant piece of glass. I walked through those endless shelves, trying to discover a way toward the door, but the shadow just faded in the dim, soft golden light with a flash of wind overcoming my collar and tie. I felt the wind rushing through my skin and my lungs, as the shadow, rustling, suddenly disappeared, with ashes muffling my sight. The smell of tobacco in the 19th century, combined with soot and roast fruit, swarmed into my nose, and I blew them out. I could imagine my distorting face, covering my face with a silk handkerchief, escaping from the mysterious place as fast as I could.</p>
<p>I hurried outside the museum, the sun going down and streetlights turning on, shadowing the dim light, punctuating the dense atmosphere of moisture and fog. It was a peaceful night, not even the wind was rushing across the street, but I could feel something uncommon approaching, trying to occupy my thoughts, driving me into a huge whirlpool I could hardly understand. I could feel my desire to return to the museum, to open the showcase, to grab the relic, and to take it out with no reason. It was going to ruin my career as a museum worker, I thought, trying to derive away this eccentric and thrilling idea. The sky was now totally dark, but I could feel the fire of desire going furious, trying to go out of my breast. I could not wait to hurry back to the museum.</p>
<p>I went back to the museum, starring at the Iron Gate and the ancient Greek pillar, starring at the magnificent characters and anaglyph on the marble roof, sinking in the strange silence of the museum night, it was like the first night when I went into the cinema, watching the famous, miraculous film Night at the Museum. I could even remember that the tomb of the Pharaoh was shaking, and the stone guardians were waving their weapons, just like waving a truck in the air. I opened the huge iron gate with all my bravery, and slowly, rambled inside the museum.</p>
<p>It was all dark. Everything was in their place, peacefully. Without people shouting, or wondering, the museum was in a strange regulatory theme, filling the air with a strange substance that calmed me down. I slowly approached the corridor where I met the shadow for the first time.</p>
<p>It was there! The shadow was still there! The glass window was open, and in the darkness of night, I could hear a rustling sound shaking in front of the dark shadow. I quickly approached, when the shadow dilated, standing up inside the dim light, and flying towards me slowly without a single sound. When I realized it, it pushed my silk handkerchief from my pocket, threw it into a huge sack (which I didn’t notice even a few seconds ago), and disappeared in the night of darkness.</p>
<p>The bell rang, and I was caught, with the crime of stealing.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The puppet circus]]></title>
        <id>https://prpkprpk.github.io/post/the-puppet-circus/</id>
        <link href="https://prpkprpk.github.io/post/the-puppet-circus/">
        </link>
        <updated>2024-03-18T08:25:32.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>There was a kid who lost in the woods. “Do not go to the circus!” So said the note written in red words, pasted on the boy’s bedside cupboard.</p>
<p>“Emm……Does it mean to the circus recently arrived at the city?” The boy was confused. Next to the note, a ticket lying on the cupboard, the boy stood up and picked up the ticket.</p>
<p>“Weird. I never purchase red ink for my pen.” Although feeling strange, the boy still picked up the ticket and put it into his pocket. “I have to go to the circus to meet my friends.” He thought as he left the room, leaving the note behind his thought.</p>
<p>It was a sunny, warm afternoon, and we could easily notice a huge, red tent was standing at the end of the rugged, country road, against the mountain filling with trees and other plantation. The boy was rushing across piles of dried soil, splitting the ash and dust onto his trousers. He held the ticket in hand, breathing, and waving his hands, as if his friends were at the tent, even not noticing his trousers turned yellow. Within only a few minutes, he arrived at the tent.</p>
<p>The boy looked around. “It is weird. Why there is no one here? It is always crowded with people cars.” He could nebulously recollect his memory last week, when the school was over, children were crowded in the tent, yawling. Starring at the huge gate, the boy shouted again and again, but only silence answered him. He could even hear the droning sun pouring the power of heat to his sweating body.</p>
<p>Wondering round and round, he finally took out the ticket. He never really looked at the ticket. It was a beautiful piece of black cardboard with a big circus logo and a gold embossed pattern. The boy turned the ticket over, and to his surprise, there was only ten: Please do not visit the circus if you are alone.</p>
<p>The boy gave a strange cry and shook off the ticket like a hot potato. All of the sudden, the light around the giant tent vanished, and fog approached as if the sun had never existed. Logs crushed on each other, like thunders, combining with the sound of leaves shuffling across the misted air. The boy panickily ran forward, only to see a pine tree blocking his path. He turned quickly to the left, but soon more and more trees emerged from the mist. “Strange, it doesn’t seem to be a forest around the circus. “ The tree frightened the boy, but they didn’t prevent him from hurrying in the endless forest.</p>
<p>The mist flew past the boy like trains filling with ghosts, branches squeaked under the boy’s feet, and he, finally, went exhausted and collapsed in the weeds. The day was getting darker, and trees seemed to circling his body, trying to take control to this unlucky prisoner. The boy opened his eyes with difficulty: a familiar footprint appeared before his eyes. He despaired: it turned out that he had never run even only a single step. Still, the boy was lifting his hands, trying to move forward, but, miserably, he discovered that he could not control his body anymore.</p>
<p>Somehow, he seemed to hear a pungent sound whispering in his ear: “There are so many people who came to see the show alone. Don’t be afraid, and you are not the only one.”The boy lost his conscious in the endless maze of forest in the circus.</p>
<p>A few days later, the circus left the mountain town. At the last show, some people, saw some familiar faces, on the magnificent stage.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>